[English subtitles are available]
[Song of the Moon]
[Episode 14]
You want to stop me from being born.
No one of you can stop me!
Oh no.
Something bad will happen.
Can't I stop you either?
Look!
This is...
Who is that?
Lord Wuxiang.
It is Lord Wuxiang.
Ge is out.
Look, it has been suppressed.
Amazing.
As expected of Immortal.
Yes.
Great!
Great.
We're saved.
This is the magic instrument that only Immortals can possess,
Moon bell.
Ge has become Immortal.
Ge,
congratulations on your out.
After a thousand years,
Immortal Palace
finally has an immortal.
It's happiness to Immortal Palace
and a blessing to the Three Realms.
How did this disaster
happen today?
Fix the Protection Spell,
reinforce the formation,
check the casualties,
and find out who she is.
What's going on?
What happened?
How did this happen?
Why is it getting dark?
Look.
Look!
Yes.
Look.
The deeper the color of the glazed fruit gets,
the fewer restrictions Immortal Palace has on us.
It looks like the cracks of Four Seasons Monument
will be deepened.
I heard that
it was a human boy.
He killed Ao Hen
with the Moon Sword.
But he can't save his own life
I play to celebrate that in this life, I could meet
a man who used Moon Sword
with a mortal body.
Lu Li,
you are the only one
who is worthy to appreciate this song.
-It is Lord Wuxiang. -Lord Wuxiang.
Lord Wuxiang is out.
Yes, Lord Wuxiang has come out.
Great.
The Immortal Palace finally has an Immortal.
Yes.
-Lord Wuxiang is finally out. -Great.
Great.
Brother...
Brother!
Clean your heart.
Ge,
you came back after experiencing hardships.
There shouldn't be any trace of the mortal world.
Why are you so distracted?
I experienced hardships with my heart.
It's inevitable to be affected.
I will clean it myself
and return to the deity whose heart is
without anger or worries.
Ge,
you've been cultivating for a thousand years,
and you have always been self-disciplined.
I
rest assured.
Brother.
Brother,
you're back.
Immortal,
disciples are waiting in the Litian Temple.
[Immortal Palace, Litian Temple]
When we were busy fixing Four Seasons Monument,
Ao Hen managed to break the Ziji Shield
and led the demons to come out.
I think
this must have something to do with
Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
And the one who played Bone-Corroding Harp
is a disciple in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
Liu Shao.
Did you really play Bone-Corroding Harp?
Liu Shao,
the Immortal is asking you.
Lu Li and I
got Bone-Corroding Harp back
together.
When the string was broken,
we fixed it together.
This is a spirit vein only a high-level demon has.
It can only be extracted in extreme pain.
If the demon doesn't have an ulterior motive,
why would he take such a risk?
So,
who gave it to you?
It's a spirit vein.
Isn't it hair?
The Zeshui Hair from ten thousand years ago
was found by you.
It was not easy.
Could it be that He Na took his spirit vein out
to save me?
Look at her.
Her words don't match.
She is out of her mind.
Liu Shao.
When I got it,
it was just said to be a single hair.
You're so eloquent and full of excuses.
How dare you say you are not the spy?
Liu Shao was hunted by Ao Hen before
and had nowhere to hide.
How could she be a spy?
Don't frame her.
That's right.
Is the Immortal Palace still unreasonable?
Fatty, Xue.
I think
you disciples
have been taught badly.
You think that the Immortal Palace
should be indebted to you and owe you
just because a few people died.
Immortal,
why don't we inform the Three Realms that
this disaster was caused by the rebellion of Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
forbid people from mourning for Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
and forbid them from accepting people's worship
to show immortal power?
Yes.
Aren't our lives lives?
-Yes. -Yes.
How can you do that?
What did they do wrong?
Under Four Seasons Monument,
Lord sacrificed himself.
Many seniors died.
They risked their lives to fight against demons.
What did they do wrong?
How dare you!
What?
Did I say anything wrong?
All of us,
from the first day we came to Marquis Wuyang's Mansion,
we were taught
to suppress demons and protect all living beings.
Just because of Immortal Palace's
suspect for no reason,
do you want to ruin our lives?
Then what is the difference
between you and those demons
who kill everyone
who gets in their way?
You dominate our lives
not because of right and wrong,
but for pros and cons.
You
are not worthy to be called the leaders of the Three Realms.
You insulted Immortal Palace!
Do you want to die?
Moon Sword...
Why do you have it?
Phoenixes choose sycamore trees to rest,
while good swords choose their owners.
Why can't I have it?
Lu Li has died.
Even the Moon Sword has a different master.
Immortal,
this woman is too unreasonable.
She must be taught a lesson.
Since you insist that Marquis Wu Yang's Mansion has done nothing wrong,
I can
give you a chance.
[Bone Melting Pool]
Come on.
Go inside.
There is a Bone Melting Pool in Immortal Palace.
It's surrounded by thorns that are ten thousand years old.
There are countless evil auras inside.
If the demons and villains are trapped inside,
they will die.
But if someone has upright and pure thoughts,
he can go in and out safely.
Are you willing to use your life to prove your innocence?
In order to save my fellow disciples who are alive
from being ruined by you,
I want to go.
Come at me if you dare.
Don't hurt my family.
Young lady,
you are quite bold.
Aren't you afraid of me?
I'm not afraid of you.
You can't kill me.
I'm waiting for you to learn hard...
I'll definitely achieve something
and won't need to be afraid of Ao Hen.
[Imperial Cosmos Hall]
Miss Xi,
it's all my fault.
Don't blame Liu Shao.
It has nothing to do with Liu Shao.
Xue, don't be like this.
You don't understand kindness.
You are different from us.
You don't have the right to scold her.
Everything she got
was earned
through her hard work.
It seems
what this woman does and thinks
is pure and upright.
Why would she destroy Four Seasons Monument?
This is...
It's not valid
to stop the trial with the help of other things.
Bracelets...
Lu Li...
No!
No. Lu Li gave it to me.
♫On rainy days, the wind blows smoke♫
Give it back to me.
♫Into circles♫
Why did it turn into this?
♫On both sides, I’m chanting♫
♫The night is sleepless♫
♫The shadows of the moon are incomplete, and people are in love♫
♫A cocoon of shadows♫
I was born with only half a heart
♫Your promise, my fate♫
Now
I have found the other half.
It is you.
♫In spring, seasons changed♫
Lu Li is dead.
♫But my heart is still the same♫
This is the only thing he left for me.
♫Back to the sky, the clouds passing by♫
Are you going to take it away from me too?
♫Is like the things we went through♫
Liu Shao?
♫Beside the lake, on the boat♫
The moon is above the willow branch.
♫The moment we passed each other♫
What a good name!
You're 18 this year.
♫Can compare with the rest of my life♫
I'm 23.
What should you call me?
Brother Lu Li.
Good girl.
♫I look at my love and send it to the clouds outside the garden♫
If you want to make a living in Marquis Wuyang's mansion,
you have to listen to me.
♫Looking at your ageless face at the end of the world♫
Give it back to me.
Lu Li gave it to me.
♫You put the winter snow in your ears and can’t hear it♫
Look,
I'm in your hands now.
I won't let anything happen to you.
♫When the flowers stop falling, you and I will miss each other♫
I will protect you.
Do you understand?
♫Everything in the world passes before understanding♫
♫After the missing, my face is still young♫
But my life is long.
What if I can't afford to hire you?
I'll sell myself to you.
A coin.
Lu Li is sold to Liu Shao.
♫The day the flowers fall in the garden, the day we meet♫
Will you never regret it?
Never.
I like you.
♫If you see me for the first time in this life, I'll forever hold it in my heart♫
I just want to be an ordinary person
and live a happy life with you.
OK, let's be a normal couple
♫Get lost in your sky♫
and live an ordinary and happy life
♫Whose wilderness♫
I go
wherever you go.
♫Clouds billow up and fade away in the four seas♫
Lu Li,
after we pull out the Moon Sword
and defeat Ao Hen,
♫The mountains and rivers after the farewell♫
remember to ask your master to come to my home to propose to me
♫Silence♫
♫Time sighs silently♫
Liu Shao.
♫Whose passing years♫
Then I...
will ask Lord to be the matchmaker
to propose marriage to you when I am back.
Lu Li!
Maybe this year
we can also choose a good day to get married.
But I will die.
I'll accompany you.
I'm really going to die.
I'll really be with you.
Even if I die,
I won't let you die.
This...
Why do I feel so familiar?
Wasn't that Lu Li?
Why did I...
Bracelet...
I have found the bracelet.
I only have you,
only have you...
Not only did she walk out of the Bone Melting Pool,
she even went through the Life Gate
and directly came to Four Seasons Monument.
The Life Path of Bone Melting Pool was originally
connected to Four Seasons Monument.
But how did she do it?
Look!
How is this possible?
Lu Li,
is it you?
How dare a human
offend Immortal?
Lu Li...
Immortal,
why does your face...
You look exactly like that mortal.
No matter if I have an appearanc, I am still me.
What are your doubts?
When Ge was promoted to Immortal,
he received mortal things,
so he looks like a mortal.
This is a good omen.
Go back first.
I have something to discuss with Immortal Master.
Yes.
Four Seasons Monument is made by the God of the Sun.
Her blood can stabilize Four Seasons Monument.
It only means...
Ge,
do you suspect Liu Shao is...
Yes.
Sun Spirit is in her body.
If that's the case,
I really underestimated her.
I thought she only had the fragment of the spirit.
I didn't expect that she would be the heir to Sun Spirit.
She can walk out of the Bone Melting Pool.
It shows that she is upright.
There must be another reason
for Bone-Corroding Harp.
Lu Li.
Lu Li,
you're Lu Li, right?
You have Sun Spirit in your body.
Stay in Xiyin Mountain,
and don't go back to the mortal world.
I won't.
I'll go wherever you go.
I am the Immortal of Xihui Mountain,
Luo Ge.
No,
you're Lu Li.
You're Lu Li.
Lu Li!
You are Lu Li.
Love is a sin.
Why are you doing this?
Liu Shao,
are you really not going back with us?
No.
There are some things
I must figure out.
Sister-in-law,
do you really think that cold Immortal
has anything to do with my boss?
Impossible.
If they are related,
how could he let you get into Bone Melting Pool?
That's right.
Look at your injury.
But after the Moon Sword left Lu Li,
it immediately took Luo Ge as his master
and got controlled by him.
Well,
that only means Moon Sword
is not a good thing.
Exactly.
It hurt you badly
and killed Lu Li.
I don't think it treats you as its owners.
It took Luo Ge as its owner obediently
just because Luo Ge is too powerful,
But Immortal Luo Ge
came out
just after Lu Li died.
Besides,
he has the same face as Lu Li.
How could a mortal Lu Li
affect Immortal?
So,
I must investigate it.
What if...
Lu Li is still alive?
Liu Shao,
we've already seen it.
No.
I've been taught a lesson before.
What I see may not be true.
I'm not going back.
Fattie,
I'll leave Xue to you.
Remember,
you must work hard when you go back.
Don't let the people in the Three Realms look down on us.
Of course.
Brothers and sisters,
let's go back.
Lord has died.
The human world
has to rely on us.
Sister-in-law,
take care.
Senior Liu Shao, take care.
Take care.
We're leaving.
How can Immortal Luo Ge
have the same face as Lu Li?
Is he really alive?
That is where the three palaces are.
This is Xiyin Mountain.
Leader Zhuo,
this place is
more elegant than other places.
This is Immortal Luo Ge's sister,
Luo Ning's residence.
In the Immortal Palace,
only her room is by the water.
Is this the person who played Bone-Corroding Harp?
I want to hear
what's special about her playing.
Zhuo,
don't get involved in this.
Otherwise,
I will remove the beads on the golden crown
of Leader Shang
and play with them.
This round is difficult
for you.
Take care.
That day,
you played the harp, right?
Play it again, and
let me listen to it.
Brahma Song?
But Bone-Corroding Harp
was taken away by the Immortal Palace.
How can I play it?
Wind chimes?
Where did you
learn this song?
I didn't learn it on purpose.
I just
saw
an old tree blooming.
Then, I suddenly got it.
I feel that
it's a song created before.
It sounds very familiar,
and it's especially nice.
I didn't expect that
you would be not only beautiful,
but also intelligent.
I dare not.
My name is Liu Shao.
You must be
the legendary Fairy Luo Ning, right?
If anyone bullies you,
just tell them my name.
Why are you injured?
Let's go.
Come in with me.
Let me put on
the new healing dew I made for you.
I promise you'll be fine.
After that,
I'll show you around, okay?
Let's go.
When I was blocked during my promotion,
I had to seal myself here
and cut out half of my heart
and send it to the mortal world to experience hardships.
Is it because
my half heart had a mortal body
that I have this face?
Since you've come back from hardships,
why bother about the shadow in the human world?
What happened on the way
is not important.
The result is your practice.
But Liu Shao
is the obstacle on your way to becoming a deity.
You must not let her stay by your side.
Are you afraid that the history of ten thousand years ago would repeat itself?
Or do you also think that
Luo Ge will be bewitched by beauty?
But what in her body
is the power of God of the Sun.
How can I not worry?
That's why I let her stay.
Her blood has the power of the God of the Sun.
It can help us stabilize Four Seasons Monument.
♫I ask the cloud and the flower♫
♫How I can stop missing you♫
♫I walk through the time♫
Isn't it beautiful?
♫Whether we can forever♫
♫Love each other like now and carve this between our eyebrows♫
What did they do to you?
There are so many wounds.
♫A white horse came and became a poem♫
It has been bald for years.
Look,
the flowers bloom as soon as you come.
[Immortal Palace, Feiyuan House]
♫Memory is beautiful and I am still loving you♫
♫In the vast blue sky, I prefer to pursue the moon♫
[Immortal Palace, Xiyin Mountain]
♫Do you know it?♫
♫Thousands of lights made it like a day♫
♫It is like my heart where you are still there♫
♫I am waiting. The moon is above the willow branch♫
Did Xiyin Mountain change its gardener?
These withered trees bloom again.
♫I only want to hold your hands and count beans of love♫
♫I am guarding you. A turning around♫
♫Exchanges staying together forever♫
♫The love is as before♫
I was curious
so I asked Immortal Master about you.
I think you need
this gift.
What is this?
This
is the new fragrance I developed.
Take it out
and drop a drop on your wrist.
Smell it, and
you can have a sweet dream.
In your dream,
you can meet the person you like
You can also tell him that
you miss him,
or
you are doing well.
Am I doing well?
Master,
I
bought you good medicine.
It will definitely cure your cough.
You are acting like a woman.
Fu,
if you dare to offend me again,
I'll destroy your demon power of a thousand years.
Luo Ge has gone through hardships and become immortal.
He is investigating the spy in Lusitai.
I have investigated the audience
on that day.
including the disciples in Marquis Wuyang's Mansion.
That day,
Liu Shao was about to finish mending Four Seasons Monument.
But unexpectedly,
she flipped the harp
and played another tune for no reason
and hit Four Seasons Monument.
The melody I played
can attack and destroy things.
As soon as I play it,
clouds will be pierced and stones will be broken.
Since Liu Shao is going to damage Four Seasons Monument,
why did she repair it before?
It doesn't make sense.
I developed so many cracks with the sound of my musical instrument.
With just one strike of Moon Sword,
Four Seasons Monument will be opened.
What about Moon Sword?
Who was using it?
It's a disciple of Marquis Wuyang,
Lu Li.
Lu Li...
is my body when I was experiencing hardships.
Back then,
in order to save Liu Shao and other people,
he used Moon Sword as a mortal
and was eventually devoured by the sword.
But Lu Li didn't use Moon Sword
to break Four Seasons Monument.
Instead, he used it to kill Ao Hen.
At least Lu Li has held Moon Sword.
You...
are not enough.
Except for Lu Li,
I have another disciple in Immortal Palace.
She'll try to get close to Luo Ge.
Lu Li is dead,
but the Moon Sword is still there.
It can't be counted as a failure.
But for you, it's hard to say.
Do you really think that
Luo Ge can't find anything?
Two magical weapons appeared at the same time.
Ziji Shield was also broken.
It should be specially designed by someone.
In my opinion,
Ao Hen
is probably just a pawn.
Liu Shao showed her magic power.
Sun Spirit fragments should be scattered around here.
Find them quickly.
Keep an eye on Liu Shao too.
Yes.
There must be traces of the spell on Sun Spirit fragments.
They'll know it's you once they investigate it.
You're going to be exposed,
but you come here
and talk with me happily.
About this,
don't worry.
My spy in the Immortal Palace
will give me Sun Spirit Fragments.
I have such a good spy.
How can I care about Immortal Luo Ge?
Instead, you need to worry about
Liu Shao.
You must kill her,
lest she really repairs Four Seasons Monument.
Your brother protects her,
while you want to kill her.
Since you brothers are not united,
why don't you replace him?
Ao Hen is dead.
The Demon Realm is in chaos.
This is your chance to win over the people's hearts.
As for the Demon King,
how can you, a half-demon, talk about it?
What's wrong?
Don't you like what your brother looks like now?
No.
I like it.
I like it
whatever my brother looks like.
But...
my brother is too pretty.
I'm afraid my brother's face
will cause trouble.
Let me do it.
I'll do it.
So...
Just say it.
There's no need to beat about the bush
between us.
Brother,
have some tea.
I
made a new friend.
She is very good-looking
She treats me well too.
But pitifully,
her life is so miserable.
Brother,
do you really not remember
what happened to you
when you were in the mortal world?
Why should I remember it?
But when you don't remember it,
someone who was with you remembers it.
What should we do?
Debt in the mortal world should be solved in the mortal world.
Even if there is something unfinished,
for us immortals, it's nothing.
Brother,
we are really brothers and sisters.
We have the same thought.
So,
I helped you
trap her in her dream with fragrance.
When she is there,
she can be with you...
no...
you in the mortal world
happily.
She can't bother you anymore.
♫How many rain seasons and rains do I need to see♫
What do you think?
♫Before meeting you♫
Is it pretty?
Yes.
♫I am destined to sink to the bottom of the sea♫
♫You come to my mind♫
♫But this moment, you believe♫
♫You are my only one. Don't hesitate♫
♫Flowers fly after the rain♫
Will she dream of Lu Li,
♫I stay there♫
half of my heart that bothers me?
♫I say I miss you. Because of your name♫
♫The rest of my life is all about you♫
♫I can't tell if it is dream♫
♫After the flower blossoms, let the love go on♫
♫I say I miss you. Don't doubt it♫
♫You exist in my life♫
♫I want to stay with you♫
♫After the spring and the winter, let the love go on♫
Okay, let's go.
I'll show you something fun.
Follow me.
What is it?
Shush.
Rabbit!
Where did you get it?
What's its name?
It's our food for tonight.
No way.
Give it to me.
♫How many rain seasons and rains do I need to see♫
Just kidding.
If you like it,
I'll get you a load of rabbits.
♫Before meeting you♫
We will keep them in the mountain.
Let's
be a pair of rabbit kings.
♫I am destined to sink to the bottom of the sea♫
How is it?
I'm afraid that
you can't even catch one
♫You come to my mind♫
♫But this moment, you believe♫
♫You are my only one. Don't hesitate♫
Catch me!
Where are you escaping?
♫Flowers fly after the rain♫
♫I stay there♫
♫I say I miss you. Because of your name♫
♫The rest of my life is all about you♫
♫I can't tell if it is dream♫
After I wake up from my dream,
♫After the flower blossoms, let the love go on♫
will I never see you again?
No.
♫I say I miss you. Because of your name♫
Because
you're also Luo Ge, right?
♫The rest of my life is all about you♫
Lu Li is me.
♫I can't tell if it is dream♫
Luo Ge is also me.
♫After the flower blossoms, let the love go on♫
I am with you
wherever you are.
♫I say I miss you. Don't doubt it♫
♫You exist in my life♫
This is Lu Li in the mortal world.
♫I want to stay with you♫
♫After the spring and the winter, let the love go on♫